

# Johnny Wang

Experienced interior designer with 7+ years of experience in color, pattern, and texture matching skills

Award-winning and certified interior designer with 7+ years of experience in creating functional and sustainable designs for 150+ clients. Have completed major projects for hotels, casinos, and high-end residential properties. Skilled in AutoCAD and Adobe Suite. Mentored 6 interior design students.

**(881)-333-8900** 



iohnny.wang@gmail.com



in Columbus, Ohio

### **Hard Skills**

AutoCAD

Adobe Suite

Sketching

Architectural detailing

On-site consultation

#### Soft Skills

Communication skills

Creative thinking

Deadline-driven

Customer service

Problem-solving

## Work Experience

2015 - Present

### Interior Designer | COSI Design House

- · Delivered functional and aesthetically pleasing designs for both commercial and residential clients.
- · Two-time winner of the Designer Magazine interior design award.

2005 - 2010

#### Founder & Interior Designer | Johnny's Design Place

- Collaborated with known design companies such as X, Y, and Z.
- Designed the State House Dining Hall, a government-owned property that greets 45,000 visitors in a month.

#### Education

### B.F.A. in Interior Design | Columbus College of Art & Design

2000 - 2004

